[Music]
our life journey is made up of various
goals we wish to fulfill this could be
going on a dream vacation buying a fancy
car purchasing our first house providing
our children with the best education
opportunities or securing a comfortable
retirement for ourselves a few simple
steps taken today towards your financial
planning can help you ensure that these
important goals of yours are fulfilled
presenting ICICI proof guaranteed income
for tomorrow
gift a savings plus insurance plan that
allows you to save systematically and
grow your money with 100 guaranteed
tax-free returns along with a life cover
so that you are assured of meeting all
your financial goals and creating a
secure tomorrow for yourself and your
loved ones
the ICICI approved gift plan comes with
three options income early income and
lump sum in this video we will look at
the gift lump sum option this option
allows you to set aside a fixed amount
from your income and invest for a
specific time period depending on your
goals and get a guaranteed tax-free lump
sum at the end of the policy term let's
understand this better with an example
Ravi Mehta is a 35 year old salary
professional with a young daughter and
is saving regularly with the primary
goal of creating a fund for his
daughter's higher education however the
returns he is getting have been
continually declining for the last few
years due to financial interest rates
also the returns are taxable making his
net returns even lower
he is in search for a long-term savings
option that will offer him guaranteed
risk-free and tax-free returns
irrespective of fluctuating markets
unstable interest rates and other
unpredictable scenarios he decides to
purchase the ICICI Pro gift plan online
with lump sum option and invest rupees
10 000 monthly from his income for 10
years by the time his daughter finishes
schooling his investment of rupees 12
lakhs will grow into a guaranteed
tax-free Corpus of rupees 20.29 lakh
paid out to him on the 15th year
and the best part this return is fixed
and risk-free irrespective of
fluctuating interest rates and
unpredictable Market scenarios
Mr Mehta will also get the dual benefit
of tax savings on premiums paid and
tax-free Returns on maturity he can also
Avail a loan against his policy in case
of any financial needs
along with a guaranteed lump sum this
plan also gives Ravi a life cover to
secure the well-being of his family in
case of any unfortunate event
buying this plan online is safe secure
and convenient plus you also get to
enjoy additional 2.5 maturity benefit so
what are you waiting for give yourself a
bright tomorrow and secure your dreams
with guaranteed tax-free returns you can
start investing at just rupees 2500 per
month visit
icicipruelife.com to know more benefits
about the plan today or call us at
1-800-209-977 and our insurance experts
will be glad to assist you foreign